<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE pdf2xml SYSTEM "pdf2xml.dtd">

<pdf2xml producer="poppler" version="0.24.5">
<page number="1" position="absolute" top="0" left="0" height="1188" width="918">
	<fontspec id="0" size="22" family="Times" color="#000000"/>
	<fontspec id="1" size="12" family="Times" color="#000000"/>
	<fontspec id="2" size="13" family="Times" color="#000000"/>
	<fontspec id="3" size="16" family="Times" color="#000000"/>
	<fontspec id="4" size="12" family="Times" color="#000000"/>
	<fontspec id="5" size="12" family="Times" color="#000000"/>
<text top="56" left="354" width="210" height="27" font="0"><b>Teaghan P. Grayson</b></text>
<text top="113" left="68" width="102" height="16" font="1">9704 Glenway Ct</text>
<text top="128" left="68" width="170" height="17" font="2">Burke, Virginia 22015-4114</text>
<text top="113" left="764" width="86" height="16" font="1">(703)965-3792</text>
<text top="128" left="675" width="175" height="17" font="2">teaghan.grayson@gmail.com</text>
<text top="160" left="68" width="79" height="20" font="3"><b>Education</b></text>
<text top="182" left="68" width="299" height="16" font="4"><b>College of William and Mary, Williamsburg, VA</b></text>
<text top="182" left="737" width="113" height="16" font="1">May 2010 - Present</text>
<text top="200" left="68" width="427" height="16" font="1">Bachelor of Arts, International Relations, Minors: Economics, Philosophy</text>
<text top="233" left="68" width="81" height="20" font="3"><b>Objectives</b></text>
<text top="255" left="68" width="712" height="16" font="1">To begin a career where I can use my skills in research and analysis for the betterment of my employer and my community.</text>
<text top="288" left="68" width="135" height="20" font="3"><b>Work Experience</b></text>
<text top="310" left="68" width="384" height="16" font="4"><b>Catholic Family and Human Rights Institute, Washington, DC</b></text>
<text top="310" left="705" width="145" height="16" font="1">May 2013 - August 2013</text>
<text top="328" left="68" width="92" height="16" font="5"><i>Research Intern</i></text>
<text top="346" left="68" width="779" height="16" font="1">Assisted with research and event planning for the Catholic Family and Human Rights Institute (C-FAM). Filed reports and briefings on</text>
<text top="364" left="68" width="752" height="16" font="1">human rights issues, such as the protection of women and children in developing countries, that were sent to members of congress.</text>
<text top="382" left="68" width="745" height="16" font="1">Blogged twice per week on topics relevent to the Catholic Church and human rights. Assisted in organinizing an event for 11 UN</text>
<text top="400" left="68" width="161" height="16" font="1">delegates and their families.</text>
<text top="426" left="68" width="282" height="16" font="4"><b>National Defense University, Washington, DC</b></text>
<text top="426" left="705" width="145" height="16" font="1">May 2011 - August 2011</text>
<text top="444" left="68" width="92" height="16" font="5"><i>Research Intern</i></text>
<text top="462" left="68" width="778" height="16" font="1">Planned three conferences for Dr. Alenka Brown and the Center for Technology and National Security Policy (CTNSP). Assisted in all</text>
<text top="480" left="68" width="778" height="16" font="1">steps of planning these conferences, including inviting attendees, creating programs with speaker bios, securing catering for the events,</text>
<text top="498" left="68" width="712" height="16" font="1">helping to set up the conference room before it began and cleaning up afterward. Took notes for Dr. Brown at meetings and</text>
<text top="516" left="68" width="767" height="16" font="1">conferences, including unclassified events she could not attend in person. Assisted in researching a variety of projects for Dr. Brown,</text>
<text top="534" left="68" width="628" height="16" font="1">including Smart Grid technology, human interoperability, and a Naval study on improving energy efficiency.</text>
<text top="559" left="68" width="361" height="16" font="4"><b>MacArthur Strategic Marketing Services, Millersville, MD</b></text>
<text top="559" left="723" width="127" height="16" font="1">June 2010 - July 2010</text>
<text top="577" left="68" width="63" height="16" font="5"><i>Consultant</i></text>
<text top="595" left="68" width="778" height="16" font="1">Compiled reports on Saudi Arabian industry and high-speed rail infrastructure for my employer to assist him in advising a client on the</text>
<text top="613" left="68" width="211" height="16" font="1">best strategy to take for his business.</text>
<text top="646" left="68" width="72" height="20" font="3"><b>Activities</b></text>
<text top="668" left="68" width="751" height="16" font="4"><b>Eagle Scout, Boy Scouts of America</b>: Received my Eagle Scout Award in November, 2009. Completed an Eagle Scout project to</text>
<text top="686" left="68" width="759" height="16" font="1">qualify for the award. Organized and led the project, which consisted of mulching a nature trail at a local rec center and putting sign</text>
<text top="704" left="68" width="771" height="16" font="1">posts along the trail. Obtained all materials (except mulch) and labor necessary for the project. Advertised the project to my boy scout</text>
<text top="722" left="68" width="221" height="16" font="1">troop and had 23 people come to help.</text>
<text top="758" left="68" width="759" height="16" font="4"><b>Assistant Leader, W&amp;M CCM Haiti Service Trip: </b>Helped lead a group of seven college students on a trip to Thomonde, Haiti in</text>
<text top="776" left="68" width="711" height="16" font="1">January, 2012. Worked at a school to fill in for absent teachers as well as helping the children and the school with odd jobs.</text>
<text top="794" left="68" width="778" height="16" font="1">Dialogued with the principal of the school to find out what they needed, notably clean water for the students. Worked with local NGOs</text>
<text top="812" left="68" width="744" height="16" font="1">to secure cheap, easy to clean water filters and training for teachers at the school to care for the filters and to teach students better</text>
<text top="830" left="68" width="674" height="16" font="1">hygiene habits. Organized fundrasing events to raise $3000 to pay for the filters and the cleaning and hygene classes.</text>
<text top="866" left="68" width="779" height="16" font="4"><b>Public Relations Coordinator, William &amp; Mary Students for Life</b>: Managed advertising for the various events put on by William &amp;</text>
<text top="884" left="68" width="756" height="16" font="1">Mary students for Life during the 2011-2012 school year. Used social media sites, such as Facebook and Twitter, to advertise these</text>
<text top="902" left="68" width="777" height="16" font="1">events which lead to a noticeable increase in turnout. Led a small team to create and distribute fliers throughout the campus of William</text>
<text top="920" left="68" width="181" height="16" font="1">&amp; Mary to advertise the events.</text>
<text top="956" left="68" width="770" height="16" font="4"><b>Study Abroad, Salzburg, Austria</b>: Studied at the University of Salzburg during the Fall 2012 semester. Classes centered on study of</text>
<text top="974" left="68" width="769" height="16" font="1">International Relations and German Langauge and Culture. Spoke German langauge during the majority of the stay and engaged with</text>
<text top="992" left="68" width="201" height="16" font="1">locals daily in casual conversation.</text>
<text top="1025" left="68" width="42" height="20" font="3"><b>Skills</b></text>
<text top="1047" left="68" width="629" height="16" font="1">Proficiency with Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Powerpoint, and Microsoft Outlook/Entourage</text>
<text top="1083" left="68" width="771" height="16" font="1">Knowledge of SPSS; able to do statistical analysis and data gathering, from basic manipulation of variables, to doing hypothesis tests,</text>
<text top="1101" left="68" width="262" height="16" font="1">to doing bivariate and multivariate regression</text>
</page>
<page number="2" position="absolute" top="0" left="0" height="1188" width="918">
<text top="55" left="68" width="722" height="16" font="1">Good Researcher; able to analyze and synthesize large sets of information and draw conclusions from it, as well as compiling</text>
<text top="73" left="68" width="604" height="16" font="1">everything into a form that can be more quickly read and understood by anyone needing the information.</text>
<text top="109" left="68" width="631" height="16" font="1">Extrovert; very good with people in a variety of social situations and skilled at communicating ideas to others</text>
<text top="145" left="68" width="457" height="16" font="1">Positive attitude; can stay relaxed, upbeat, and productive in stressful situations</text>
<text top="181" left="68" width="736" height="16" font="1">Experience in professional environments allows me to focus more on my work than adapting to the workplace for the first time.</text>
<text top="217" left="68" width="634" height="16" font="1">Good writer; able to clearly express and advocate positions in a clear and concise manner through my writing.</text>
<text top="253" left="68" width="717" height="16" font="1">Good orator; able to speak clearly and engage in lively debate with others who disagree with me without allowing emotional</text>
<text top="271" left="68" width="284" height="16" font="1">attachment to get in the way of making my point.</text>
</page>
<outline>
<item page="1">Teaghan P. Grayson  </item>
<outline>
<item page="1">Education</item>
<item page="1">Objectives</item>
<item page="1">Work Experience</item>
<item page="1">Activities</item>
<item page="1">Skills</item>
</outline>
</outline>
</pdf2xml>
