<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE pdf2xml SYSTEM "pdf2xml.dtd">

<pdf2xml producer="poppler" version="0.24.5">
<page number="1" position="absolute" top="0" left="0" height="1188" width="918">
	<fontspec id="0" size="19" family="Times" color="#000000"/>
	<fontspec id="1" size="14" family="Times" color="#000000"/>
	<fontspec id="2" size="19" family="Times" color="#000000"/>
<text top="105" left="385" width="149" height="24" font="0">Kimya Farivari</text>
<text top="130" left="343" width="232" height="18" font="1">6109 Clearwood Rd, Bethesda MD</text>
<text top="149" left="372" width="175" height="18" font="1">kimyafarivari@gmail.com</text>
<text top="206" left="135" width="92" height="23" font="2"><b>Education</b></text>
<text top="249" left="135" width="367" height="18" font="1">Towson University, Towson MD, Graduated May, 2015</text>
<text top="268" left="135" width="610" height="18" font="1">Bachelor of Science in Family and Human Services; Services To Children and Youth Track; </text>
<text top="287" left="135" width="604" height="18" font="1">Significant coursework in Special Education; Member, Towson Student Council on Family </text>
<text top="306" left="135" width="274" height="18" font="1">Relations; Member, Alpha Gamma Delta.</text>
<text top="346" left="135" width="337" height="23" font="2"><b>Employment and Community Service</b></text>
<text top="388" left="135" width="322" height="18" font="1">Special Olympics Maryland, Intern, Spring 2015</text>
<text top="408" left="135" width="608" height="18" font="1">Assisted as coach and instructor with adult athletes in multiple sports. Coordinated sporting </text>
<text top="426" left="135" width="607" height="18" font="1">events and location management.  Acting Assistant supervisor for the Spring 2015 Aquatics </text>
<text top="445" left="135" width="620" height="18" font="1">Qualification Games at Loyola University.  Led Young Athletes Program weekly, guiding 2-7 </text>
<text top="464" left="135" width="622" height="18" font="1">year olds with activities to emphasize physical activity and cognitive and social development. </text>
<text top="483" left="135" width="222" height="18" font="1">Input scorekeeping data on GMS.</text>
<text top="521" left="135" width="310" height="18" font="1">Emeritus, Towson, Maryland, Intern, Fall 2014</text>
<text top="540" left="135" width="602" height="18" font="1">Served as a nursing home volunteer intern. Assisted staff in the Memory Care Department; </text>
<text top="559" left="135" width="609" height="18" font="1">worked directly with elderly suffering from Traumatic Brain Injuries and Dementia; created </text>
<text top="578" left="135" width="461" height="18" font="1">activities for the elderly to enhance their cognitive skills and memory.</text>
<text top="616" left="135" width="420" height="18" font="1">Sibley Memorial Hospital, Bethesda MD, Intern Summer 2014 </text>
<text top="635" left="135" width="637" height="18" font="1">Worked in the Labor and Delivery department directly with nurses to make sure all mothers and </text>
<text top="654" left="135" width="627" height="18" font="1">their newborns had a positive experience. Worked on Excel; transferred patients and newborns </text>
<text top="673" left="135" width="587" height="18" font="1">throughout the hospital; transferred blood work; assisted discharging patients and babies.</text>
<text top="711" left="135" width="321" height="18" font="1">American Tap Room, Bethesda MD, 2012-2014 </text>
<text top="730" left="135" width="170" height="18" font="1">Hostess and Receptionist.</text>
<text top="770" left="135" width="388" height="18" font="1">English Village Home Daycare, Bethesda MD, 2011-2013 </text>
<text top="789" left="135" width="603" height="18" font="1">Child Care Supervisor; created and implemented educational lessons for children ages 2-5; </text>
<text top="808" left="135" width="616" height="18" font="1">oversaw outdoor recreation activity; supervised meal time; provided interactive story lessons.</text>
<text top="847" left="135" width="376" height="18" font="1">Katherine Thomas School, Rockville MD, Summer 2012</text>
<text top="866" left="135" width="606" height="18" font="1">Teaching Assistant/Substitute Teacher. Served as caretaker for children with developmental </text>
<text top="885" left="135" width="624" height="18" font="1">disabilities. Significant experience working with a range of moderate to severe developmental </text>
<text top="904" left="135" width="583" height="18" font="1">disabilities; created an orderly workspace to allow for productive learning environment. </text>
<text top="944" left="135" width="109" height="23" font="2"><b>Office Skills</b></text>
<text top="987" left="135" width="592" height="18" font="1">Highly Proficient in MS Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Photoshop, Excellent oral and written </text>
<text top="1006" left="135" width="645" height="18" font="1">communication skills; Excellent computer research skills; Ability to work in team environment or</text>
<text top="1025" left="135" width="253" height="18" font="1">to work independently with initiative. </text>
</page>
<outline>
<item page="1">Education</item>
<item page="1">Towson University, Towson MD, Graduated May, 2015 Bachelor of Science in Family and Human Services; Services To Children and Youth Track; Significant coursework in Special Education; Member, Towson Student Council on Family Relations; Member, Alpha Gamma Delta.</item>
<item page="1">Employment and Community Service</item>
<item page="1">Special Olympics Maryland, Intern, Spring 2015</item>
<item page="1">Assisted as coach and instructor with adult athletes in multiple sports. Coordinated sporting events and location management. Acting Assistant supervisor for the Spring 2015 Aquatics Qualification Games at Loyola University. Led Young Athletes Program weekly, guiding 2-7 year olds with activities to emphasize physical activity and cognitive and social development. Input scorekeeping data on GMS.</item>
<item page="1">Emeritus, Towson, Maryland, Intern, Fall 2014</item>
<item page="1">Served as a nursing home volunteer intern. Assisted staff in the Memory Care Department; worked directly with elderly suffering from Traumatic Brain Injuries and Dementia; created activities for the elderly to enhance their cognitive skills and memory.</item>
<item page="1">Sibley Memorial Hospital, Bethesda MD, Intern Summer 2014</item>
<item page="1">Worked in the Labor and Delivery department directly with nurses to make sure all mothers and their newborns had a positive experience. Worked on Excel; transferred patients and newborns throughout the hospital; transferred blood work; assisted discharging patients and babies.</item>
<item page="1">American Tap Room, Bethesda MD, 2012-2014</item>
<item page="1">Hostess and Receptionist.</item>
<item page="1">English Village Home Daycare, Bethesda MD, 2011-2013</item>
<item page="1">Child Care Supervisor; created and implemented educational lessons for children ages 2-5; oversaw outdoor recreation activity; supervised meal time; provided interactive story lessons.</item>
<item page="1">Katherine Thomas School, Rockville MD, Summer 2012</item>
<item page="1">Teaching Assistant/Substitute Teacher. Served as caretaker for children with developmental disabilities. Significant experience working with a range of moderate to severe developmental disabilities; created an orderly workspace to allow for productive learning environment.</item>
<item page="1">Office Skills</item>
<item page="1">Highly Proficient in MS Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Photoshop, Excellent oral and written communication skills; Excellent computer research skills; Ability to work in team environment or to work independently with initiative.</item>
</outline>
</pdf2xml>
